<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LocalizationPackages>
    <LocalizationPackage Lang="English">
        <!-- Encyclopedia Entries -->
        <Text key="Ency_OxygenGeneration">Oxygen Generation</Text>
        <Text key="EncyDesc_OxygenGeneration">Oxygen generation is essential for sustaining life in underwater habitats. Each base compartment consumes oxygen, and larger or more complex bases require greater oxygen production to remain habitable. Specialized oxygen generators convert water into breathable air, powered by the base's energy reserves. To ensure safe atmospheric conditions, install sufficient generators to match your base's size and monitor oxygen levels as you expand or modify your habitat.</Text>
        <Text key="Ency_SmallOxygenGenerator">Air synthesizer</Text>
        <Text key="EncyDesc_SmallOxygenGenerator">The air synthesizer is a compact oxygen generator designed for smaller bases or as a supplementary source of breathable air. It efficiently converts water into oxygen, providing a steady supply to maintain safe atmospheric conditions. Ideal for early base development or as an emergency backup, the air synthesizer is an essential component for any underwater habitat.</Text>
        <Text key="Ency_LargeOxygenGenerator">Atmospheric processing unit</Text>
        <Text key="EncyDesc_LargeOxygenGenerator">The atmospheric processing unit is a high-capacity oxygen generator designed for larger bases or those with higher oxygen demands. It utilizes advanced technology to efficiently convert water into breathable air, ensuring a stable and sufficient oxygen supply for extensive underwater habitats. The atmospheric processing unit is crucial for maintaining safe atmospheric conditions as your base expands and becomes more complex.</Text>
        <Text key="Ency_LargeOxygenGeneratorFragment">Atmospheric processing unit fragment</Text>
        <Text key="EncyDesc_LargeOxygenGeneratorFragment">A fragment of an atmospheric processing unit. Scan to learn more.</Text>

        <!-- Buildables -->
        <Text key="SmallOxygenGenerator">Air synthesizer</Text>
        <Text key="Tooltip_SmallOxygenGenerator">Supplies a small amount of oxygen to your base.</Text>
        <Text key="LargeOxygenGenerator">Atmospheric processing unit</Text>
        <Text key="Tooltip_LargeOxygenGenerator">Supplies a large amount of oxygen to your base.</Text>
        <Text key="LargeOxygenGeneratorFragment">Atmospheric processing unit fragment</Text>
        <Text key="Tooltip_LargeOxygenGeneratorFragment">A fragment of an atmospheric processing unit. Scan to learn more.</Text>

        <!-- UI -->
        <Text key="OxygenEfficiency">Oxygen efficiency</Text>
        <Text key="OxygenNoPower">No power</Text>

        <!-- Options -->
        <Text key="ProductionRateSmallOxygenGenerator">Air synthesizer production rate</Text>
        <Text key="Tooltip_ProductionRateSmallOxygenGenerator">Adjust the oxygen production rate for air synthesizers.</Text>
        <Text key="ProductionRateLargeOxygenGenerator">Atmospheric processing unit production rate</Text>
        <Text key="Tooltip_ProductionRateLargeOxygenGenerator">Adjust the oxygen production rate for atmospheric processing units.</Text>
    </LocalizationPackage>
</LocalizationPackages>